你们看，丑裸男在收拾东西
Guys,look! Ugly Naked Guy's putting stuff in boxes.
看样子我们的裸友要搬家了
I'd say our naked buddy is moving.
讽刺的是大部分的箱子 都标示着“衣服”
Ironically,most of the boxes seem to be labeled "Clothes."
我会怀念那个大屁股的
I'm going to miss that big old squishy butt.
鸡肉炒饭没了
And we're done with the chicken fried rice.
如果他要搬走 我可以去把那里租下来
If he's moving,maybe I should try to get his place!
好主意 跟你们遥遥相对多好玩啊
It would be so cool to live across from you guys.
那我们就可以玩电话游戏
We could do that telephone thing...
你一个罐子，我们一个罐子 中间有一条线
...where you have a can,we have a can...and it's connected by a string.
或者我们也可以打真的电话
Or we could do the actual telephone thing.
糟糕，他的那个地方粘到胶带了
He's got packing tape stuck to where you really don't want it.
快撕掉啊，肥仔
Get it off,fat man! Get it off!
糟糕，他想慢慢撕下来
Oh,no,he's trying to pull it off slowly.
相信我，撕胶带一定要快
Take it from me,if you're gonna pull tape off yourself,it's gotta be in one quick motion.
就像那样
Like that.
本集播出：“所有人都知道了”
The One Where Everyone Finds Out
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
天哪，我爱死这层公寓了
Oh,my God. I love this apartment!
很完美吧？
Isn't it perfect?
我居然没发现这里有这么棒
I can't believe I never realized how great it is!
因为你的目光 会马上移到丑裸男身上
Because your eye goes to the big naked man.
太棒了，你最好赶快去申请 否则我会抢先
It's amazing!Hurry up with an application,or I'll beat you to it.
没想到会有这一天 我要去用丑裸男的厕所了
Well,I'm going to use Ugly Naked Guy's bathroom.
你看，是莫妮卡和钱德
Look! There's Monica and Chandler.
喂，你们好，喂
Hey,you guys!
钱德和莫妮卡！钱德和莫妮卡
Chandler and Monica!
天哪
Oh,my God!
钱德和莫妮卡！
Chandler and Monica
我的眼睛！我的眼睛
Oh,my eyes!My eyes!
菲比，菲比，没事的
It's okay!
不！他们搞在一起 我知道，我知道
-They're doing it! -I know!-I know!
你知道？
-You know?
对，我知道，乔伊也知道
Yes,I know it. Joey knows,
但罗斯不知道 所以你别再叫了
but Ross doesn't,so stop screaming!
怎么了？
What's going on?
怎么了？ 没事
-What? -Nothing!
我们只是好兴奋你要搬来这里
We are so excited that you'll get this apartment!
这里的确很棒 天哪
Looks really good.Looks pretty good!
快过来啊
Get in here! Come on!
中央咖啡馆
你是说每次莫妮卡和钱德 去洗衣服或买东西或…
You mean whenever Monica and Chandler...were doing laundry or going grocery shopping?
她每次跟伤心的琳达讲电话
The time Monica spent on the phone with Linda from camp?
做吧，做吧，电话也是，做吧
Doing it,doing it,phone,doing it.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it!
真是太好了…对他来说 她可以有更好的对象的
I think it's great. For him.She could do better.
你们好
Hey,you guys.
乔伊，快过来 怎样？
Come here!
菲比发现莫妮卡和钱德的事了
Phoebe found out about Monica and Chandler.
就是他们是朋友，如此而已？
You mean how they're friends and nothing more?
不，乔伊，她知道了
Joey,she knows.
我们刚才在丑裸男的公寓 看到他们隔着窗户在做
We saw them doing it through the window.
应该说是靠着窗户在做
Actually,we saw them doing it up against the window.
我们看到他们私通
We saw them fornicating.
他们知道你知道 但是不知道瑞秋知道？
So they know you know,and they don't know that Rachel knows?
对，但现在这些都不重要了
Yes,but it doesn't matter who knows what.
我们有三个人知道 就可以告诉他们了
Now enough of us know that we could just tell them we know.
我再也不必说谎保密了
All the lying and the secrets will finally be over.
或者我们也可以不告诉他们 自己来找点乐子
Or,we could not tell them we know,and have a little fun.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
譬如每次他们说要洗衣服 我们就给他们一堆衣服洗
If they say they are doing laundry,we'll give them laundry to do.
我喜欢
I would enjoy that.
不，你知道怎样更好玩？ 告诉他们
You know what would be even more fun? Telling them.
听起来不好玩 那就让它变好玩
-That doesn't sound like fun. -So we'll make it fun.
我们可以学理发店四重唱
We'll do it like a barbershop quartet!
我们知道…
We know,we know,we know
不，我想照菲比的做法
No,I want to do Phoebe's thing.
我没办法再… 你只要别说我们知道就行了
I can't take…You don't have to do anything. Just don't tell them we know.
不要，我没办法再保密了
I can't take anymore secrets.
我有你们的秘密，他们的秘密 还有我自己的秘密
I got your secrets,their secrets,secrets of my own.
你才没有秘密
You don't have any secrets.
是吗？你就不知道我有个企鹅抱枕叫哈吉（童话片《哈加邦奇》）
Well,you don't know about Hugsy,my bedtime penguin pal.
所以…我们要怎么耍他们？
So How are we going to mess with them?
你可以利用室友的身分
You could use your position as the roommate.
我就运用我最大的本钱 我的性感
And I would use the strongest tool at my disposal.My sexuality
孩子们
Hello,children.
仔细看，学着点 别吃我的饼干
Watch. Learn. And don't eat my cookie.
你穿这件外套真好看 是吗？
That jacket looks great on you.-Really?
对，这个料子摸起来好软… 二头肌先生
-The material is so soft.Hello,Mr. Bicep.
你有在健身吗？ 我有在挤
You're working out?I try to squeeze things.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
如果你真的想知道，我… 我不能告诉你
If you really want to know I can't tell you this.
菲比，你什么都可以告诉我
You can tell me anything.
事实上我就是不能告诉你 但我又最想告诉你
Actually,you are the one person I can't tell this to.And the one person I want to the most.
怎么了？
What's going on?
因为我很久没跟男人在一起了
I just haven't been with a guy in so long...
有时你一直寻寻觅觅 却没发现他就在你眼前喝咖啡
...and sometimes you're looking for something...and it's right there in front of you,sipping coffee
我说太多了吗？
Oh,no. Have I said too much?
总之你考虑一下，我会考虑的
Just something to think about. I know I will.
你好可爱 你怎么会这么可爱？
You are so cute.How did you get to be so cute?
我爷爷是瑞典人 我奶奶其实是只拇指兔
My grandfather was Swedish.And my grandmother was a tiny little bunny.
你变得更可爱了
Now you're even cuter.
这简直是今天的民意 什么？
You know,that is a popular opinion today,I must say.
今天在咖啡馆有一件怪事 我觉得菲比在勾引我
The weirdest thing happened at the coffeehouse.Phoebe was hitting on me.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
是真的，菲比觉得我很有魅力
I think Phoebe thinks I'm foxy.
不可能
It's not possible.
抱歉，只是在菲比眼中 你的迷人是无性的
I'm sorry,Phoebe's just always thought you were charming...in a sexless kind of way.
这种话真是百听不厌
You know,I can't hear that enough.
抱歉，你应该误解她的意思了
I just think you misunderstood her.
我没有误解，好吗？ 她只差没扑上来
I didn't,okay? She was all over me.
她还摸我的二头肌尖叫
She touched my bicep,for crying out loud.
这个二头肌？
This bicep?
我现在没挤它
Well,it's not flexed right now.
为什么你这么难相信 菲比对我有意思？
Why is it so hard for you to believe that Phoebe could be attracted to me?
我没有啊 女生都会对你有意思
It's not.All the girls are attracted to you.
你有拇指兔的血统
You're part bunny.
莫妮卡，你要干什么？ 要不要一起去看电影？
Mon,you want to come see a movie with us?
事实上我正要去洗衣服
Actually,I was going to do some laundry.
钱德，要不要一起去？ 好啊，我跟你一起去
Want to do it with me?Sure,I'll do it with you.
太好了，等一下
Okay,great. Hold on a second.
拿去
Here you go.
这样我就轻松多了，谢谢
That would really help me out a lot. Thanks.
我的硬币应该不够 我这里有
You know what? I don't have enough quarters.I have quarters!
太好了 我们可以洗一整晚的衣服了
Great. Now we can do laundry all night. All night laundry!
罗斯，公寓申请得怎样？
Hey,any word on the apartment yet?
我打过去问 原来丑裸男要自己转租
I called there,and it turns out Naked Guy is subletting it.
而且已经有一大堆申请者  哦不
He's already had 100 applicants.-Oh,man.
没关系，我跟他们的差别是…
-No,no,it's okay.Because you know what the difference between them and me is?
你有尿床的历史？
Your history of bedwetting?
你怎么可以说出来
Hey,I trusted you,man!
总之 差别是我占了优势
Anyway,the difference is...I've got the edge.
我知道这样有点奸诈 但我送了点东西去贿赂他
It's not exactly ethical,but I sent him a bribe...to tip the scales in my direction.
从窗户能看得到
You can see it from the window.
是那个打了蝴蝶结的弹珠台吗 不是
Is it that pinball machine with the big bow on it?
那辆新的登山车？ 不是
That new mountain bike?
那你送什么？ 一篮英式小松饼
What did you send?A basket of mini muffins.
但桌上全都是英式小松饼 哪一篮是你送的？
There's a whole table of them. Which one did you send?
小的那一篮
The small one.
什么？你真以为那篮松饼 能帮你争取到公寓？
You actually thought that basket was going to get you the apartment?
对，我们办公室曾经收到一篮 大家都爱得不得了
Someone sent us a basket at work,and people went crazy over those muffins.
那天真的很高兴
It was the best day.
你的工作让我觉得好悲惨
Your work makes me sad.
真是的，我好想要那层公寓
Oh,man,I want that place so much!
我还以为一定会成功
And I was so sure that was going to work.
那12块钱算是一去不复返了
There's 12 bucks I'll never see again.
菲比，想看电影就得快了
We'd better go if we want to catch that movie.
再见
Bye.
钱德再见，我已经开始想你了
Bye,Chandler. I miss you already.
你看到她不正常而且还捏我吗？
Did you see that? The inappropriate,and the pinching?
我看到了
Actually,I did.
你相信她对我有意思了吧？
So do you believe that she's attracted to me?
天哪，她知道我们的事了？
Oh,my God! She knows about us!
真的？ 菲比知道了，她想吓我们
Are you serious?She knows,and she's trying to freak us out!
这是唯一的解释
That's the only explanation!
那我好捏的屁股 和激凸的二头肌呢？
But what about my pinchable butt and my bulging biceps?
她知道了
She knows!
乔伊
Joey
咋了？
Yeah
菲比知道我们的事了
Phoebe knows about us.
我没告诉她们
I didn't tell them!
她们？她们是谁？
Them?Who's "them"?
菲比和乔伊
Phoebe and Joey.
乔伊
Joey
和瑞秋
And Rachel.
我想告诉你们 但她们逼我不能说
I would have told you,but I promised not to tell.
天哪 对不起，那现在没事了吧？
Man. I'm sorry.But it's over now,right?
你们可以告诉她们你们知道了
You can tell them you know they know,
我就可以恢复我什么都不知道的状态
and I can go back to knowing nothing!
除非… 没有除非，现在就要了结
Unless…Not "unless"! This must end now!
她们还自以为高明
They think they are so slick messing with us.
她们不知道我们知道她们知道
But they don't know that we know that they know.
所以… 没错，耍人的变成被耍的
So The messers become the messees!
拜托啦，说出来多好玩 我们知道…
Come on,you guys. Think how much fun it would be to tell.We know,we know,we know
什么？
What?
对喔，你们不懂
Oh,that wasn't you.
不 罗斯，别再折磨自己了
Honey,you got to stop torturing yourself
你去找别的房子嘛
Why don't you find another apartment?
我这个月已经看了上千个房子 没有一间比得上那一间
I've already looked at 1000 apartments this month.None of them even compares to that one.
有一间不错但是我得跟 一家亚美尼亚人一起住
Well,except for one,but I would have had to share it with an Armenian family.
那个奶奶很喜欢我
Grandma really liked me.
但我想要丑裸男的公寓
But I want Ugly Naked apartment!
你知道你应该怎么做吗？
You know what?
你应该找出他的嗜好 拿来跟他套交情
You should find out his hobbies and use that to bond with him.
例如我对乔伊有所求 我就会聊…三明治
Like if I wanted something from Joey...I would strike up a conversation about sandwiches
或是我的内衣
...or my underwear.
我在听
I'm listening.
看吧
See？
好棒的主意
That is a great idea!
而且我了解丑裸男 因为我们偷窥了他5年
And I know Ugly Naked Guy because we've been watching him for five years.
所以我又重新占了上风
So that gives me back my edge!
好，他有一张跳床 被他跳坏了
Let's see now. He had the trampoline.He broke that.
他有一双重力靴 也被他穿坏了
-He had gravity boots. -He broke those too.
所以他喜欢破坏东西
So he likes to break stuff.
好，我得去接班 不过我会想出来的
I've got to go pick up Ben. But I will figure something out.
他之前不是有一只猫吗？
Didn't he used to have a cat?
别提那个，会害他心情不好
I wouldn't bring that up. It would bum him out.
可怜的猫咪 没看到大屁股压下来
Poor cat never saw that big butt coming.
喂？
Hello
在，等一下，她就在旁边
Hold on a second,she's right here.
钱德找你
It's Chandler.
嗨，你
Hello,you.
菲比，我一整天都在想你
Phoebe,I've been thinking about you all day.
你之前的提议 说我不心动是骗人的
You know that thing you said before? I was intrigued.
是吗？
Really?
对，乔伊晚上不在
Joey won't be here tonight.
你要不要过来 我让你摸我的二头肌
Why don't you come over? I'll let you feel my bicep.
甚至是别的地方
Or maybe more.
我待会再给你答复，再见
I'll have to get back to you on that.Okay bye
天哪，他找我去摸他的二头肌 和别的地方
He wants me to come over and feel his bicep and more!
不会吧？ 是真的
Are you kidding?
他居然背着莫妮卡…
I cannot believe he would do that to Mon
乔伊，他们知道我们知道吗？
Joey? Do they know that we know?
不知道 乔伊
No.  Joey
他们知道你们知道了 我就知道
They know you know.I knew it!
我本来会说：谢天谢地 大家都知道了，总算没事了
I would say,"Thank God! Everybody knows! It's finally over!"
但每次说都没用
But that hasn't been working for me.
真不敢相信那两个人
I cannot believe those two!
他们以为他们可以耍我们 想耍我们是吧？
They thought they could mess with us? Trying to mess with us?
他们不知道我们知道 他们知道我们知道了
They don't know that we know they know we know.
乔伊，你不能说
Joey,you can't say anything.
我也不想说了
Couldn't if I wanted to.
你好，我是罗斯盖勒 我也申请要租你的房子
Good evening,sir. I'm Ross Geller. I'm one of the applicants.
我知道竞争很激烈，但是…
I realize that the competition is fierce but....
抱歉，我注意到你光着身体
I'm sorry,I can't help but notice that you're naked.
我为你鼓掌 我也好想光着身体
I applaud you.Man,I wish I was naked.
看起来好舒服
I mean,this looks so great.
这正是上帝造人的本意
That is how God intended it.
你看她们多慌
Look. They're panicked!
她们绝对会退缩 没错
They'll totally back down.
好，他敢约我就敢去
If he wants a date,he's going to get a date.
我要过去了 好，性感一点
I'm going to go in.Be sexy.
拜托
Please.
钱德，我晚上可以过去
I'd love to come by tonight.
真的？ 当然，就7点吧？
Really?Absolutely. Say,around 7?
好
Yes
很好 我很期待跟你发生性关系
I'm really looking forward to you and me having sexual intercourse.
快来看！丑裸男有裸友来访
Hey,check it out!Naked Guy's got a naked friend.
真的
Oh yeah
天哪，那是我们的朋友
Oh,my God! That's our friend!
是裸罗斯
It's Naked Ross!
你还要小英式松饼吗？
Would you like another mini muffin?
吃吃看蓝莓口味，很好吃
Try the blueberry,they're delicious.
上场啰
Showtime!
瑞秋，拿香水来 好
Rachel,get me perfume.
乔伊，帮我拿一瓶酒两个酒杯
Joey,can you get me a bottle of wine and glasses?
谢谢，但我要的是 没把手的玻璃杯
All right,thanks,but glasses that do not have handles and that are glass.
我要酒不要橄榄油
And wine that is not olive oil.
放心好了
It'll be great
只要让她以为你想跟她上床 她绝对会吓到
Make her think you want to have sex with her and it will freak her out.
我到底得撑到什么程度？
How far am I gonna have to go with her?
别紧张，她会比你先投降
She'll give in way before you do.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
因为你跟我同一队 我这一队总是赢
Because you're on my team. My team always wins.
赢这种事？
At this?
总之去吓她，快去
Just go get some! Go!
好，我会站在门外听 好
Now,I'm going to try to listen from right here.
等一下
Oh,wait.
好主意
Good idea.
等等 别血本无归了
Don't give away the farm.
菲比
Phoebe
钱德
Chandler
进来吧
Come on in.
我正要进去
I was going to.
我带了酒来，你要吗？ 好啊
I brought some wine. Would you like some?Sure.
就我们俩了，紧张吗？
So here we are.Nervous?
我？不会，你呢？
Me? No. You?
不会，这样正合我意
I want this to happen.
我也是
So do l.
我去放点音乐
I'm going to put on some music.
乔伊喜欢吓鸭子
Joey likes to scare the duck.
我跳舞给你看好了
Maybe I'll dance for you.
你真美
You look good.
谢谢
Thanks.
你说这种话 让我好想扯掉你的毛衣背心
You know,when you say things like that,it makes me...want to rip that sweater vest right off.
不如进房里再说吧？ 真的吗？
Why don't we move into the bedroom?Really?
你不想吗？
Do you not want to?
不是，只是我想先脱掉衣服 让你替我擦乳液
First I want to take off all my clothes...and have you rub lotion on me.
听起来不错
That would be nice.
我去拿乳液
I'll go get the lotion.
情况完全失控了 她要我帮她擦乳液
It's way out of hand. She wants me to put lotion on her!
她在唬你
-She's bluffing!
她没打算放弃，她还这样
-She's not backing down.She went like this
他没打算放弃，他去拿乳液了
He's not backing down. He went to get lotion.
他是钱德，你可以搞定他
It's Chandler. You can take him.
还记得你曾经把他骂哭吗？
Come on. Don't you remember when you made him cry using only your words?
真是的，你们还没好吗？ 我想坐我的椅子
Aren't you guys done yet?I want to sit in my chair!
乔伊，菲比一突破钱德的心防 这一切就结束公开了
The sooner Phoebe breaks him,the sooner it's over and out in the open.
我喜欢
I like that.
我知道，让他看你的胸罩 他怕胸罩，他解不开
Show him your bra. He's afraid of bras. Can't work them.
乔伊
Joey
你没把扣子都挑开
You didn't rip off any buttons.
经验老道
It's not my first time.
你给我回去，色诱她让她屈服
Go back there and seduce her till she cracks!
好，等一下
Give me a second.
你打扫过吗？当然了
-Did you clean up in here? -Of course!
你要走了？
You're going?
除非你跟我走，爱人
Not without you,lover.
这是我的胸罩
So this is my bra.
非常非常好看
It's very,very nice.
过来，我很高兴我们要做爱了
Well,come here.I'm very happy we're going to have all the sex.
你是该高兴，我的身体很柔软
You should be. I'm very bendy.
我要吻你了 除非我先吻你
I'll kiss you now.Not if I kiss you first.
接下来就只能接吻了
I guess there's nothing left for us to do but kiss.
终于来了
Here it comes.
我们的初吻
Our first kiss.
好，你赢了
You win!
我不能跟你上床
I can't have sex with you!
为什么？ 因为我爱莫妮卡
-And why not? -I'm in love with Monica!
你什么？
You're what?
没错，我爱她，我，爱她
That's right!I love her!I love her!
我爱你，莫妮卡
I love you,Monica.
我也爱你，钱德
I love you too,Chandler.
我以为你们只是搞在一起 我不知道你们相爱
I thought you were doing it. I didn't know you were in love!
伙计
Dude!
向菲比致敬，强劲的对手
Hats off to Phoebe. Quite a competitor.
提醒一下你的胸部还晾在外面 天哪
May I say your breasts are still showing.God.
就这样，结束了 大家都知道了
All right! So that's it?It's over. Everybody knows!
罗斯还不知道 对，请你们先别告诉他
Actually,Ross doesn't.We'd appreciate it if no one told him yet.
就是这里，全新罗斯的新家
Well,here it is.A new place for a new Ross.
我一布置好就请你和同事来坐
I'll have you and the guys from work over,once it's furnished.
很高兴看到你重新振作
It's nice to see you back on your feet.
我是振作了 脾气暴躁的事都过去了
I am that,and the whole rage thing is definitely behind me.
我认为你是不是该回馆里上班了
I wonder if it's time for you to rejoin our museum team?
那就太好了 我已经准备好重回岗位，我…
That would be great.I am totally ready to come back to work.
什么？不
What？No
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
从我妹妹身上起来
Get off my sister!